on that day humanity received a grim
reminder that this scene has been
parodied so much that no one could take
it seriously anymore thanks are going to
eat us because we're terrible but we
have long and there's no way I can break
through the front door
probably oh god we gotta say mom put
your back into it
I've no beer I'm in a diaper - yeah
thank God Cory I need you to tell them I
can write my mom fuck your mom oh god
this is not what I thought when I click
this link no no no no no no no that's
that's not a minute no no no no no no
that's my plan mMmmm I love ya notice
Aaron how are you feeling from this day
I swear I'm gonna kill every last thing
but not before I dance in the grade when
I showering in the blood of all the
times I massacres I will know the day
every last damn wonder he's still going
every time we'll try it by that arenít
but don't fucking dare shut the fuck up
so they like Titan oh my god welcome to
military school all this training will
probably be useless because 90% of you
will die anyway start characters
introduce yourselves
I'm internet me I have a great astronaut
I can I'm going to be forgotten I'm
going to be alive well I'm going to be
an actual interesting Tara shoutout gene
or Zhang come back when you're a main
character hey hold on a second I have
screen time don't listen to him you're
my main character up Marco come back
when you're not a disposable character
gratulations are graduating you are now
officially certified cannon fodder now
have all the weapons I need to kill the
Titan actually last time I checked edge
isn't actually a weapon don't listen to
her
those stupid Titans of spinach danced
against me
what do you say I get to my face a
little bit the Titans have it later
looks like we get the fight time item
slightly front full of the bona fide
advice I strongly disagree on your side
to the day into the show
I guess myself everyone is bad except
for me
design the night your boyfriend brother
is dead hey he's not my boyfriend yet
gross do you even know why he means so
much to me here Mikasa have this dumb
scars oh my god good maybe one do start
dating an American you like it and it's
alright living anymore
hi did you see that time what do you
think it could possibly be Aaron Aaron
there and probably Aaron seriously who
else is it going to be oh come on
that's way too up oh look it's actually
Aaron oh fuck you all do you have
exactly five minutes to explain yourself
before we blow your brains out army
everyone thinks I'm now a threat to
humanity it's up to you to convince them
I trust you'll know how to zoom oh okay
maybe instead of killing our only hope
we should use them the product oh oh
that's a great plan sir you should
probably tell everyone why close enough
we're doing tank back along the tigrin
so here is what was going to do he does
realize he's like 200 feet up now right
take our line and turn it upside down
critical fellows I know he has
absolutely no idea but that is not the
black does anyone have any questions
alright did you catch all that together
and so triggered by his height himself
so he punches himself in the face yes
hey Aaron guess what
you're at I bet do it do it again
now wait we should probably get him to
carry the bolt out of the way I think
it's quite heavy
excuse me I'm walking here where am I
wait a minute you're the Derby core
scouting regiment scouting the Recon
Corps wait yes and I'm captain Levi what
was that ignore that so Aaron remember
this key which opens your basement
that's gonna be a huge plot point now
will you mind telling us what did it
yeah I remember my dad told me before
hey Dad what's in our basement Oh y'all
think so and it's called gourry the
fucking manga god damn it everybody job
alright in the trial of whether or not
we should I do Eren Jaeger well both
sides please state their cases Kim don't
fucking kill me compelling argument how
does the wall religion view this as a
follower of the wall it is our belief
that any foreign object will pose a
great threat to us as foretold long ago
by our founder and supreme prophet Lord
Trump does the defendant have anything
to say okay you can get through this the
best way you know how the shouting
really laughs off my problem captain
Aaron's enjoying it your ain't stop
enjoying it oh boy yeah Aaron oh this
really how the fujiyoshi totally what
enough of this I proposed that from now
on that Aaron will be supervised by me
privately at all times
god damn it sustained no no no this is
all fair girls now think you have this
weird dominatrix thing going on with
each other now that that's over allow me
to introduce my crew dead ones a two did
three and Petra I'm the only one
everyone cares about because I'm a cute
girl what about her hi make me horny did
I just hear that correctly yes no never
geez serve a court and out but first
we're clean Oh God seeing you clean
makes me so worried what what
wait how long are we going to be riding
on these horses how about five episodes
or so what have we gone from years
passing in a single episode to spending
half an arc on a fucking horse
what is this Ark even about that times
got an SS Oh what the fuck is that
don't worry Aaron it's all part of
Maryland's failsafe plan it's all part
of our Huan's fail-safe plan it's in
success mission fail
Levi squat get her Oh No Levi squad
they're dead
that's right now
oh my god Aaron can you stop getting
heated already Jesus Christ so I have to
do everything myself
well I don't know about you but I'd call
this mission a complete bust
yes in every day for this survey Corps
my entire team is dead you know what I
was feeling a little bit down but we
figured out any as the female Titan even
though it was blindly obviously everyone
watching even for blind people and I
have an absolutely foolproof plan to
lure her into a trap
what's the plan Annie come with us
please please please no
Wow all right now would be a great time
to get angry that's my secret cap I'm
always angry
ah God so much was something supposed to
happen
I'm not really cool in my head let me
keep another shot here intruders with
high-end try are you okay I'm not trying
hard enough
what do you want me to know how God
heard us tied up again I got that
is it just me or does this look like
very forceful Titan sex God don't make
it weird Armin alright any baby just
where I want you oh what the fuck is
this bullshit nah that's fucking axe
well or one in a few days you've cost
hundreds of lives yours worth of
collateral damage and all you could show
for is a person oh we can't even touch
now do you have anything to say yes then
every day for this survey court would
you let my mom die you bastard I'm sorry
okay I only never secret ending of
running away Joe shows Reverend Aaron
what are you talking about your mom just
died it is now time for a jojo's
referent it's always time for Joe's
Reverend Verizon games I was making a
joke as reference fuck is going on hey
guys hope you enjoyed the episode thank
you very much this month to Jericho tell
Gabe Brown wise Gabriel so shit you
ruined the whole episode
Vincent Mooney Wow can I never enough
and page one for sports me and helping
to make this video possible
if you enjoyed this episode and check
out my other animated minutes that I've
done and as also like to thank all my
cast members and my editor for making
this video as great as it was and on
time too
I'm not going to be in Japan next week
but I will have videos up in my absence
so until then I've been giggles and I'll
see you all next time